ooyyo.com 2014-06-10

# Privacy OOYYO Network

##### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you respond to a survey or fill out a form. In those cases you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Our servers may collect some of your personal information such as IP addresses and destination URLs, in order to analyze site behavior and resolve potential technical and other issues.

##### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience** (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * **To improve our website** (we continually strive to improve what we offer on our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * **To process transactions**. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * **To utilize proper technical maintenance of the site**. 
  * **To provide new and improved services on the site.**. 

##### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.

##### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow it) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

##### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our rights, property, or safety, or those of others. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

##### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

##### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act).

##### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

##### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section which contains terms of use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.ooyyonetwork.com/terms/>

##### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

##### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

##### Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may [contact us here](http://www.ooyyonetwork.com/contact/).

* * *
